YUMI ICHINOSE AND SEX THERAPIST A
CAUGHT KISSING IN THE RAIN!
They got some
pretty good shots of you, huh?
- Please forgive me.
- Hm.
Hm.
Look, you can date whoever you want,
and you don't have to apologize.
But a sex therapist? Really?
- Ugh.
- Uh, Mr. Kujo.
It's not like
either of them were cheating.
And the studio has decided
that she will remain on the air.
- All right.
- Mm.
Regardless of all that,
there's still our audience to consider.
And it's their reaction that concerns me.
Because Yumi is our innocent anchor,
like it or not.
The problem with that
is that I've never made that claim.
Our viewers decide the
personality of female reporters. Right?
Hmm.
But then… if we take her off the air,
it could come back to haunt us
and turn into some big thing.
All right, then. Keep her on.
- Do the show as usual.
- Very good, thank you.
I'm done. You can take it from here.
- Thanks.
- Yes, sir.
Do yourself a favor, Yumi.
Don't give the press
anything more to run with.
Right.
Ah…
- Is tomorrow Friday?
- Yes.
That means Old Man Marujima's
on tomorrow.
Right, the old man who loves gossip.
Yep, that's the one.
A few days ago,
right before the commercial break,
he blurted out something
about the daytime host's alleged affair.
Then there was the time
he mentioned that guy's hair transplant.
What a nightmare!
Uh…
If this is going to be a problem, I…
Well…
I'll give the old man
a talking-to before the show.
Just get on with your day,
Yumi, don't worry.
- Thank you, sir.
- Don't let me down.
Thanks again, sir.
I feel bad that you got dragged into this.
I should've been more careful.
It's okay.
How are you doing? You okay, Yumi?
It was buried on page nine,
so it shouldn't be a big deal.
But…
they said I shouldn't see you for a while,
so the press will let the story go cold.
Hmm.
Hmph.
And that viewers decide on
the personality of a female reporter.
That really didn't sit well with me.
So I can date whoever I want, but
scandals don't suit my innocent persona.
And uh… my image has to align
with what the public has decided for me.
As if I had no say in the matter.
I get what you're saying.
But you… you shouldn't dwell on it.
Thank you.
CTN CENTRAL TELEVISION
- Good morning.
- Morning.
See that article about Yumi?
- Yes!
- Can you believe it?
I saw it at checkout, so bought it!
Unreal! I mean,
what is a sex therapist, anyways?
- Who does that for a living?
- I know, right?
- You think he actually does anything?
- Like what?
Comforting her by having sex with her?
Oh my God. I can't believe
Yumi goes to places like that!
Why else would she go there?
- Can't judge a book by its cover!
- Thanks, everyone, good work!
I never would have
guessed it in a thousand years!
Excuse me, Miku?
I wanted to… apologize.
About the article.
I'm sure you've heard, right?
I'm sorry for all the trouble.
Are you wandering the halls
apologizing to everyone like this?
Huh?
Whoever you decide to go out with
is really no one's business but your own.
Apparently, Shun was shocked,
but I have no idea
why he would be, though.
Why decide to open
a restaurant in this old house?
That looks delicious!
Firstly,
I just love things with a history.
And I find it particularly interesting
to incorporate older things
in today's society.
Amazing.
So, what part of the restaurant
would you say is your favourite?
Oh, I'd have to go with the staircase.
You can actually feel the house's history
with each creak as you climb the stairs.
That is so charming!
- Back to studio.
- That's all our time.
- Thank you so much.
- Three, two…
I have to tell you that,
during the recording of this story,
the restaurant was packed.
It's obvious how much
people love this place.
Before I was married,
I lived around the corner.
- Really?
- Have you ever been there?
No, actually.
- But it looks delicious.
- Sure does.
I can attest to that.
The chili shrimp was to die for.
It was just so fresh and juicy.
Oh, I'm gonna start drooling!
- Marujima is really on today.
- Mmm.
Guess my little warning worked, huh?
And now, we'll leave you
with Yumi's Feel-Good Shot of the Day.
Wow!
- It makes me smile.
- Great shot!
Yeah! Everyone at that restaurant
just seemed so happy to be there.
- That is it for "On the Street Corner."
- Speaking of pictures, Yumi…
Huh?
That picture of you kissing in the rain…
it looked like it was
straight out of a movie.
Uh… anyone special?
Uh…
Yeah, let's, uh… make sure
we discuss that after the show.
- Right, Maru?
- No.
I'm pretty sure that
our viewers would like to hear
from Miss Ichinose herself.
Uh, well…
I'm not so sure that she wants to, uh…
I don't, uh…
I, uh… think you might be, uh…
interested to know that I'm currently
seeing that man in the picture.
Ooh, and there it is.
No, no, no, no, no!
Why the hell would she say that?
Yumi!
But we've, uh… only just started dating.
And I appreciate
how interested everyone is.
- But it would be great to get space.
- This is kind of interesting…
How long has this been going on?
- …outside the house…
- Hi there, followers.
I'm at the actual house
of the so-called sex doctor.
- Let's see if he's got anything to say.
- There he is! There he is!
Doctor, how about a few words
for my followers?
- How did you and Yumi first meet?
- Did you know she'd go public?
What do we have to do to get
sexy therapy from you?
- What kind of sex do you teach?
- How does one become a sex therapist?
- All right, enough.
- Are your sessions private?
- Or group therapy?
- Excuse me! Move aside, people!
We are not giving
any interviews at this time.
Let the doctor through.
Move aside, please!
If you want to speak to the doctor,
make an appointment.
Our office hours are displayed here.
Thank you.
Have a good day! Thank you!
- Just a few words, doctor.
- We'll wait all day here if we have to!
- Are you in love?
- This is crazy.
I feel like I'm in a zombie movie!
I never thought
anything like this would happen.
So, uh…
where did you meet that reporter, anyway?
Huh? We went to high school together.
Shimotori Clinic, hello?
Why the hell didn't you tell me?
We're not giving interviews at this time.
Did it never occur to you
to tell me you know a celebrity?
- I'm a huge fan of hers.
- Shimotori Clinic, hello?
- I want an introduction.
- For an appointment?
- So, uh…
- What for?
I told you, I admire her!
- Yes.
- Oh, jeez!
There are some wack job
YouTubers out there!
Our neighbours aren't gonna like this.
We might have to shut
the clinic for a bit.
What do you mean by that?
This is the best thing for us!
Yes, you're confirmed for 3:00 p.m.
- I don't want it to get that busy.
- Certainly.
Thanks, Ms. Tanaka,
we'll be expecting you.
I'm so sorry,
but 3:00 p.m. is already taken.
- Could I get a business card?
- Oh, 4:00 p.m. is also booked, I'm afraid.
- There.
- Thank you.
- Kimizu and… Right, YouTube.
- Yes. Uh-huh.
Got it. Can you remember
when your symptoms started?
And what is it
that brought you here today?
I want you to tell me how I can…
date a hot reporter like you did, doctor!
What?
I wanna give her multiple orgasms, doc.
Like in erotic anime stories.
Uh…
I want you to teach me the techniques
to make her whole body shake and tremble.
Uh, well, I just can't
stop getting erections…
- Uh-huh.
- What should I do about it?
Don't be shy about this.
This is exactly what we do here.
This is what sex therapy is.
I actually thought it was
sort of something like…
"I'm gonna kiss you now.
Is it okay if I kiss you now?"
"Or maybe I can kiss your ears.
Would you like that?"
So, does sex therapy…
mean I get to have sex with you, doctor?
What?
Finally, I drift off to sleep. Mmm.
I'm calm at last,
and my erection's gone too,
and then I hear, "Ah, ah, ah!"
From next door, I hear,
"Ah, ah, ah, ah!" Like that.
"Oh yeah!"
And then it gets erect again, damn it!
And it keeps going and going.
P-p-p-pulsing!
And then I hear it again, oh!
"Ah, ah, ah!" P-p-p-p-p-pulsing!
The Japanese man's once proud pecker
has weakened,
and so the country has now followed suit!
If a man's penis is good,
his country is good.
Wouldn't you agree with that, doctor?
Uh-huh.
Doctor, are you ready
for your next patient now?
Sure.
Please, come on in.
Oh, thank you.
- Ah.
- Ah. Go ahead, sit down.
Uh, sorry, but…
could I please talk to you alone?
Oh, uh…
So, what exactly concerns you, sir?
Uh…
It's nothing like that.
Okay.
That photo I took…
REPORTER
TAKEAKI KITANO
…was pretty good, huh?
Thanks to Miss Ichinose,
it's gotten quite the response.
A new relationship announcement.
So, I'd love to hear
your side of the story.
I don't like being cornered like this.
You wouldn't have agreed to an interview
if I'd asked you directly, now, would you?
If there are any false statements
on the medical questionnaire,
we won't be able to conduct
a proper session.
The things I wrote are true.
I don't believe in fabricating anything.
You know?
You're not going to turn away a patient
just because you don't like them, are you?
Okay, listen.
Let's play a game.
If you answer one of my questions,
then I'll answer one of yours in return.
That way, we'll both get
what we need out of this session.
I don't see the benefit
of playing this little game of yours.
Just give it a try.
Do you know what this is?
I will now open up the genital's chakra.
SEX THERAPIST TENSHIN'S UTERUS HEALING
Hmm.
Mmm…
Ah… Oh!
There's talk that this guy's
gathered together troubled women
and has made a harem for himself.
And on the Internet,
they're saying Yumi Ichinose
might be one of the girls
you've got in your own harem.
- I'm nothing like that guy, believe me.
- Of course you're not.
And that's why you've gotta tell them
yourself, in your own words.
Because otherwise, I'll just have
to give them my impression,
without any input from you.
All right, I'll go first.
Where did you first meet Miss Ichinose?
We've known each other for years now.
You met at school, right?
According to the rules,
isn't it my turn now?
On your questionnaire,
I see you wrote
that you don't believe
that sex enriches your life.
Could you elaborate on that, please?
Sex is only fun
when you are a young person.
Once you become
a middle-aged couple like us,
neither one of you
feels like doing it anymore.
On yesterday's broadcast, she said that
you two had just started dating.
Is that true? Or have you
actually been dating longer?
Uh…
No, we officially started
seeing each other last weekend.
Last weekend. So, wait…
You weren't actually dating
when that picture of you
kissing in the rain was taken?
Okay!
That means that
Miss Ichinose took you home
before you two technically started dating.
And why did you start seeing each other?
You said earlier
that neither of you feels
like having sex anymore, right?
Do you honestly believe that your wife
feels the same way about this?
Well, I've never asked her directly, but…
one day, she just turned to me
and said she couldn't.
That was actually two years ago!
Did you ever ask your wife why?
What the heck would I do that for?
Uh… A doctor with a young hot
television personality for a girlfriend
wouldn't understand how it feels.
Look, when your own wife rejects you,
it pretty much means you're done as a man.
All right.
I'd like you to bring your wife
to our next therapy session.
- It's important to hear both sides of the…
- Is this how it works?
You pretend to listen to people's issues
and pry into their sex lives, is that it?
Make you feel superior?
Everyone in the world,
doesn't matter who you are,
has concerns they're reluctant to discuss.
That's why… I wanna try
and be of help here.
Mr. Kitano,
please, rest assured.
When it comes to sex,
no one is sure about anything.
You sound like a real quack.
RECEIPT
I'd like to make
another appointment, please.
Oh, the doctor said your wife would be
joining you at your next appointment.
I guess she will.
Please let us know
when you're both available.
Thank you.
Okay…
He'll probably stretch
the truth a bit, then.
I apologize.
I shouldn't have said anything.
There's no need to apologize.
You were blindsided.
Still, that guy's got some guts, huh?
Pretending to be a patient
to get an interview?
I feel so bad.
Because of me…
…your image is gonna be ruined.
Classic Ichito.
Always thinking of others
instead of yourself.
You think so?
Yes, I do.
And anyway, the reaction
hasn't been bad so far.
I think we'll be fine.
I looked myself up online today.
"Answering an unkind question
with a smile,
Miss Ichinose shows her true worth."
"TV hostess Ichinose praised
for unwaveringly announcing
her relationship status."
"Experts are saying Ichinose
didn't just confirm her relationship,
but also showcased
her way of life to all."
It's funny, isn't it?
Even the studio didn't get that upset.
So I think,
even if a new article comes out,
I'm sure it won't have that big an effect.
Okay.
You're a strong woman, you know?
I had no choice but to be tough.
Hey, listen to this one.
"Japanese companies should learn
from Miss Ichinose."
"Her problem-solving skills
are top-notch."
"Just watch
her relationship announcement."
That's incredible.
"Learning a thing or two from Miss…"
Uh…
Hey, I'm home!
There you are.
I'm so tired.
Look at this.
- Hmm?
- Here.
- I want you to teach me…
- What is this?
- Huh?
- Look at it.
I'm afraid we don't teach those
kinds of things here at this clinic, sir.
I TRIED THE SEX THERAPY TREND
There must be something you can do!
Wow!
IS THE NURSE SKILLED TOO?
Like some kind of sex therapy technique
or some trade secrets you could share?
Something like that.
I wanna give her multiple orgasms, doc.
Like in erotic anime stories.
I thought you were working
at Tenkeikan University.
Yeah, uh, but this is--
You said you worked in dermatology, right?
So you lied.
What the heck is a sex therapist, anyway?
Unbelievable.
Were you analyzing our sex life too?
Like…
"Oh, so this is how she reacts
when I do this to her"?
No. Uh…
Sex therapy isn't doing stuff like that,
it's more--
No, I'd rather not hear about it, thanks.
- What are you doing?
- What do you mean, what am I doing?
- Look, I need time to think.
- What?
- I can't talk to you right now.
- No, no, wait, wait…
- I said not now!
- Just give me a second, okay?
KAZUYA SAIKAWA
Oh…
Hey, bro.
What on earth are you doing?
What do you mean?
Rumors are running rampant here.
They're saying you're working
at some shady clinic.
You gotta give me a break.
I'm not gonna get on your case
about being a nurse
like Mom and Dad do.
At least get a job at a reputable place.
Don't make the Saikawa Hospital look bad.
SHIMOTORI CLINIC
Okay, you're booked for 4:00 p.m.
We'll see you then.
Excuse me, doctor?
Can we open up now?
Even though Yuta's not here?
Oh, he's running late?
Yeah, go ahead.
Then can you please handle the sign?
Oh, yeah.
Damn Yuta.
I told him it was his big break.
Hello, Shimotori Clinic.
- Yes. You wanna come…
- There you are.
- How are you?
- Can I have your name, please?
Clara Suzuki. Okay.
Come on. Come on!
- All right. See you at 2:00 p.m. Thanks.
- Something wrong?
I have to resign.
What?
I'm sorry. I'm quitting.
What's going on, Yuta?
I found something else I want to do.
Thank you for everything.
THE SEX THERAPY WORLD'S MAVERICK
DECLARES WAR!
Well, you see, I have quite literally
opened the flood gates
for dozens of women
who are struggling
with penetration issues.
Oh.
That's why I wouldn't mind going
head-to-head with Dr. Shimotori at all.
Which sex therapist
can give women more pleasure?
Let's see who's better!
I bet I know who is!
Are you actually challenging him?
Oh, my therapy is dynamic,
his is all theoretical.
Oh, I see. Wow!
- Thank you for today, sir.
- My pleasure.
Why would anyone
interview a guy like that?
It's ridiculous how low the media will go.
Anyone can claim to be a sex therapist.
You just never know who's real or not.
That's what makes it so awful.
There are certified people
like you, Ichito,
who provide medical
and counselling services,
and then there are the likes of him.
I wish you had to be
legally qualified to do this.
But, you know,
the fact that people end up
going to guys like that
just shows how serious their issues are.
That they can't
open up to anyone they know about it.
Even if they know it's shady,
they still go.
They're grasping at straws.
Hey.
Are you okay with
being thought of like that?
The public thinks you're the same
as that clown, you know.
That's just… so ridiculous.
I know.
Maybe Yuta had people around him
who thought the same thing.
That would explain things.
Then do something about it.
This is your chance, Ichito.
Sex therapists are
in the spotlight right now.
Show people what
they're supposed to be like.
- Are you saying that I…
- Who else could do it?
This affects me too, you know that, right?
Look,
if things stay this way,
people with real issues won't have
anyone to turn to anymore.
They'll just continue
to suffer in silence.
Are you okay with that,
Dr. Shimotori?
SHIMOTORI CLINIC
PATIENT QUESTIONNAIRE
WAKAKO KITANO
I'm Ichito Shimotori, sex therapist.
Oh.
It's nice to meet you.
I was the one who suggested
a couples counselling session today.
I need to make sure you consent to this.
It's just a formality.
Uh, yes.
My husband told me a bit about it.
Yeah, so it's the same format
as it was the last time?
We answer your questions
and you answer ours, right?
- Right.
- Mmm.
So, uh, let's begin.
I'm told that…
there's been no sex in your relationship
for over two years, is that right?
I'd like you to tell me how
you feel about that, Wakako.
Ooh, how I… feel?
Please, rest assured.
When it comes to sex,
no one is sure about anything.
Pfft.
Yes, all right, but…
well, you know, at my age,
it's pretty difficult
to discuss issues like that.
Age has nothing to do with it.
There are physical changes that
happen in our lives, emotional shifts,
and we often don't understand
what's going on.
The same thing can be said about
sexual changes that we're experiencing.
I can't have…
sex anymore.
I can't have sex with my husband anymore.
I said, "Just go have
some sex if you want to."
Oh, come on.
- You know I won't do that.
- Uh…
Doctor…
Would it be all right if we spoke alone?
I just don't think that I…
can be completely forthcoming
with my husband here.
Are you all right with that?
And don't worry, um…
I'll answer all the questions
you want me to,
as soon as you come back, all right?
I appreciate this.
Would you like to continue?
Yes. I would, thank you.
So, now, why is it you feel
as though you can't have sex anymore?
Um…
It hurts.
It started a little over two years ago.
Um, uh…
I know what's supposed to happen
when I get aroused.
But it's just very dry.
And penetration really hurts.
I was even forcing myself to do it.
But the next day,
it was really painful.
And I just
couldn't take it anymore.
Physically, but
also mentally.
So, then you chose not to tell him
what was really wrong?
Yes.
So, what have you heard?
The guy Ichinose is seeing.
Yeah, that's right, that Shimotori guy.
Yeah, whatever you got.
I'll buy any information you have.
First of all, you should know that
sex is not something
you're obligated to partake in.
The mere term "sexless"
makes it sound like
you're expected to be sexually active,
whether you want to be or not,
regardless of your age or anything else.
But that's not true.
The most important thing right now,
and don't forget this,
is how you feel about it.
Huh.
Uh…
It's just that it's the pain
that's making me not wanna do it.
I wish I could.
I'd love to have sex again.
I know what that must
sound like at my age.
So if you really want to
but feel you can't,
I'd like to help you make that happen.
For the both of you.
Yes.
Huh?
Ichito, what…
Why are you here?
Sorry! I might've screwed up! I…
Were you supposed to be here today?
Let me check.
Oh, yeah! I mixed up your sessions.
Oh! I can't believe I actually did that!
You might as well just sit down.
Uh…
Uh… uh, sure.
Hey. Oh, thanks.
Ahem. So you come here too, Dr. Shimotori?
Yeah.
Everyone has an issue
they might be struggling with.
So, what should we do now?
I seem to be double-booked here,
and it's not like I'm gonna
kick one of you outta here.
So, then, I think what I'll do
is cancel both appointments.
And I'm just gonna go
and have a nice cigarette.
Oh.
My next appointment is only in an hour,
so make yourselves at home.
Might as well take advantage of this,
since the two of you can't really
meet in public now anyway.
So, um, take your time.
Enjoy.
That, uh…
was a setup, wasn't it?
I think so, yeah.
So?
Well, I managed to open the door for them.
Whether they decide to walk through it
or not is up to them.
You said before…
that you couldn't do it right now.
Is that why you come here?
Hmm.
Don't you think it's time you told him?
You've been like this for a long time.
And he needs to know the reason for it.
Tell me…
what are you thinking right now?
I'm thinking that your hand…
feels so warm.
I hope you get over this.
And I also hope
that one day…
you and I can really connect, you know?
That we…
can be together physically.
I'd love that.
Thank you.2
KAWAWA SHRINE
Huh.
Marin and Yuta, I…
Oh.
Marin, I think you can call it a day.
Thank you.
Ah. Thank you, doctor.
You got a minute?
- Listen, regarding today, I--
- I'd like you to… have a look at this.
I went out there today myself.
I think you recognize that,
don't you, doctor?